## **Christian Henrique Rezende**

Santa Rita do Sapucaí/MG Age: 29 years Phone: +55 (35) 99985.0734 E-mail: christian.henriquerezende@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/christianhrezendefullstack/

## What is my goal?

Work as React Native Developer.

### My resume

I am a Senior React Native Developer with 10 years of experience in software development, capable of working with large and small teams while maintaining a good quality standard and with deep knowledge in WEB and mobile applications development.

I have excellent interpersonal skills, which allow me to communicate effectively and work well in a team, which means I can motivate people and increase productivity. As a React Native Developer, I can plan, build, and deliver quality solutions.

I developed and implemented several features for the areas of insurance, onboarding, banking applications, LMS systems, and urban private transport management systems, among others, obtaining good feedback and contributing to the team to deliver good deliveries.

I have frontend knowledge in Javascript, React JS and React Native, NextJS, HTML, CSS, Firebase, Android, and IOS technologies. I also work in the backend with the programming languages Java, Lambda, NodeJs, and databases PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, and others.

I also have experience with the Azure DevOps and AWS platforms and worked with the Scrum methodology.

## **Experiences**

**Vortigo** • Porto Alegre/RS • 04/2022 – 03/2024 Mid-sized technology solutions company Front-end developer Responsibilities:

- Creation and maintenance of VCS repositories using git and Azure repositories.
- Planning, development, and implementation of financial management software using ReactJS.
- Planning, development, and implementation of urban private transport management system software in ReactJS.
- Planning and development of tokenized asset management software in ReactJS.
- Assistance, monitoring, and planning of financial management software solutions in React Native.
- Participation in iOS application development training with View Code.
- I am monitoring the mobile development of an IOS financial management application.
- Implementation of unit tests and integration tests to ensure greater quality and stability of the developed functionalities.
- Training and guidance in the development of unit tests for software in Javascript and ReactJs.

# Fullstack Java and React Native developer Responsibilities:

- Planning, development, and implementation of LMS system solution in ReactJS.
- Maintenance, development, and implementation of LMS solution in Java using Spring Boot.
- Maintenance and creation of tables using MySQL.
- Creating an asynchronous job routine for updating user scores with Spring Quartz.

## Main results obtained:

- Quality improvement of project source code.
- Improvement in project architecture.
- Improved communication between teams.

- Improvement in receiving feedback.
- Contribution to a banking solution for several countries.
- Contribution to the delivery of an LMS system for a large retail client.
- Contribution to the delivery of an expense management system.
- Quick learning of iOS development with Swift.

## Nova Tendência LTDA • São Paulo/SP • 05/2019 – 03/2022

Medium-sized technology solutions company specializing in insurance companies and financial markets.

Fullstack Java and React Native developer

### Responsibilities:

- Creation and maintenance of VCS repositories using git and GitLab.
- Analysis and definition of functional and non-functional requirements for assistance modules offered by an insurance company.
- Planning, development, and implementation of an assistance module offered by an insurance company, in React Native.
- Maintenance, development, and implementation of assistance module services offered by the insurance company, in Java using Spring Boot.
- MySQL, DynamoDB, and Redis database maintenance.

#### Main results obtained:

- Quality improvement of project source code.
- Improvement in project architecture.
- Improvement in receiving feedback.
- Contribution to a national banking solution.
- Knowledge of understanding requirements by participating in the entire planning and information collection process with the client.
- Improvement in interpersonal relationships by working allocated to the client.

## NPDI - FAI • Santa Rita do Sapucaí/MG • 02/2017 – 11/2018

Small Research, Development, and Innovation Center.

Software Developer

## Responsibilities:

- Analysis and definition of functional and non-functional requirements for an Android application for promotions and information for brand-producing mobile devices.
- Creation and maintenance of VCS repositories using git and bitbucket.
- Development and delivery of an Android application for promotions and information for a brand producing mobile devices in Java.
- Development and modeling of UMLs for an LMS education system for children.
- Planning, development, and implementation of LMS solution in Java using Spring Boot.
- Planning, development, and implementation of a financial management mobile application with Javascript using React Native.
- Participation in first customer contact meetings and understanding the requirements.

#### Main results obtained:

- Delivery of mobile applications for a well-known brand in the market.
- Delivery of solutions covering back-end and front-end.
- Improved understanding and collection of requirements from the customer.
- Contribution to the research and development core of a teaching center.
- Delivery of LMS solution to client.

## Keymax • Santa Rita do Sapucaí/MG • 02/2014 – 02/2017

Small software development company.

Software Developer

## Responsibilities:

 Development and implementation of desktop solutions for vending machines with communication via serial port and machine protocol, for major brands in the market, using Java and JavaSwing to build interfaces.

- Development and delivery of an Android application for product distribution for a large national distributor.
- Development and delivery of an Android application for product distribution for a large national distributor.
- Development of inventory control software with communication with proximity sensors using C and Arduino programming language.
- Coordination of development team and definition of solutions.
- Monitoring the implementation and installation of vending machines for promotional campaigns.

## Main results obtained:

- Delivery of mobile applications for a well-known brand in the market.
- Delivery of application solutions for vending machines.
- Experience working with embedded software.
- Knowledge of Java and Android.

#### Education

Bachelor's degree in information systems FAI - Centro de ensino em gestão, tecnologia e educação Finished at: 12/2016

## Languages

- Português Native fluent.
- Inglês
  Advanced C1
  USK (Callan Method)
  In progress.

## **Extra activities**

- iOS Developer Thiago Aguiar Em andamendo.
- Clean Code and Clean Archtecture Rodrigo Branas 24 horas 2023
- DevReactJS DevPleno 2020
- Docker: Ferramenta essencial para Desenvolvedores Udemy 5,5 horas 2019
- Units Tests JAVA: Domine JUnit, Mockito e TDD Udemy 7 horas 2017
- NodeJS e MongoDB Udemy 15 horas 2017